like most families we have a lot of
health expenses not covered by a
provincial health care plan and we don't
have group health coverage at work so we
got flexcare with flex care we're
protected from the high cost of
prescription drugs dental care and
vision care and many other health care
expenses and I know if one of us gets
seriously ill or has an accident we've
got the coverage we need flexcare
protects you from expenses not covered
by your government health insurance plan
like prescription drugs dental care
vision care home care registered
specialists and therapists or other
unexpected and expensive health care
costs and we only pay for the coverage
we want and need flexcare is also
affordable and there's no medical
questionnaire required for many flex
care plans call right now and get your
free no obligation information package
don't let unexpected health care
expenses threaten your family's
financial well-being call right now for
your free information package flexcare
from manulife financial